[{"answer": "No.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 9, "question": "Did the president call?", "qSentId": 8}, {"answer": "Well, they all have something different.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "What do they need from somebody like you?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "It's not a say, it's putting him back in state.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "When that specific thing is happening, what do you say?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "Well, you know, if you're thinking about yourself in a moment like that, you can't really serve, so then it would be all about you.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "I mean despite all these incredible things that you've experienced, to have the president of your country call you in his great hour of need?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "Self-doubt as often as you do.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "Do you personally ever have crushing moments of self-doubt?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "That was pretty horrific.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "Now be honest, when you first heard that, what was your reaction?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "Well, clearly it's not just about inner self-belief, it's really about people getting to the truth.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "How helpful is that to exuding the kinds of inner self-belief that you clearly have?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 147, "question": "Did she ever tell you she loved you?", "qSentId": 146}, {"answer": "Sounds like perfect.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "OK?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "I'm a strategist.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "What does he need?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "In one minute or two?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "It's the health side.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "What's the last one of your five points?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "I love the way you were laughing so uncomfortably at yourself dancing there.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "Well, I mean, could you imagine if you were dancing like that?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "Pretty much, yes.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "Oh, it is?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "Hardly.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "Do you still look on scenes like that with great affection or does it become this terrible curse you wish you'd ever been involved with?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "\"Seinfeld\"?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "I think I never really caught up to how big -- honestly to how big it was until right before we ended.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "At moment when you first start making (INAUDIBLE), at what moment do you start thinking -- actually this could be huge?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "I swear to you.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "I don't remember.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "Didn't like 100 million people watch that?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "It was like a Super Bowl, yes.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "If I'm exaggerating, go with me.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "Do we have a fact checker here?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "We get together on a daily basis.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "Do you have like little \"Seinfeld\" reunions in some dingy little bar in Manhattan?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "We do see each other on occasion.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "Do the ships just pass out of the port and that's it?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's a couple things.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "What is it about that show, do you think?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "Yes, we're going to have to now.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "Don't you have a bleeper here?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "I have more sympathy for all women in government.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "Did you have more or less sympathy for her by the end of your process, just on what it takes to be a vice president?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "No, not more Sarah Palins in my opinion.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "More Sarah Palins?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "Well, it's interesting because all of these issues are -- trans-vaginal probes and --", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "No, I mean just generally for women in America right now?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "I know.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "Are you expecting some sharp flip-flopping?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "I love it.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 585, "question": "What do you make of your country right now generally?", "qSentId": 584}, {"answer": "I have no idea.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "What is the solution for America?", "qSentId": 593}, {"answer": "For my children, I want my children to be active.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "How are we going to get there?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "That's good.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "What else?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "Yes, it's why you should be running for office.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "You do?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "I would go on the anti-transvaginal probe brigade.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "What office do you think I should run for?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "I'm not sure any part of it.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 653, "question": "What part of that character did he fall in love with?", "qSentId": 652}, {"answer": "Yes, definitely.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 657, "question": "Yeah, you think?", "qSentId": 656}, {"answer": "Well, let's see, first of all, we're separating.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 675, "question": "How have the pair of you, who are in the same profession, managed to stay happily married for 25 years?", "qSentId": 674}, {"answer": "Here's the deal.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 681, "question": "How did you know he was the right guy?", "qSentId": 680}, {"answer": "I do feel lucky.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 695, "question": "Do you feel lucky?", "qSentId": 694}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 703, "question": "Do you make each other laugh?", "qSentId": 702}, {"answer": "No, it's not an \"SNL\" battle.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 707, "question": "Because there's an \"SNL\" battle every day?", "qSentId": 706}, {"answer": "No, I'm kidding.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 716, "question": "Are you seriously about to split up?", "qSentId": 715}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120505pmt", "aSentId": 731, "question": "What could go wrong?", "qSentId": 730}]